[
{
"Question":"1. Which is the nearest star to planet earth?",
"A": "Sun",
"B": "Moon",
"C": "Pluto",
"D": "Jupiter",
"Answer": "Sun"
},
{
"Question":"2. Which of the following is used in pencils?",
"A": "Graphite",
"B": "Silicon",
"C": "Charcoal",
"D": "Phosphorous",
"Answer": "Graphite"
},
{
"Question":"3. The great Victoria Desert is located in?",
"A": "Canada",
"B": "West Africa",
"C": "Australia",
"D": "North America",
"Answer": "Australia"
},
{
"Question":"4. The largest gold producing country in the world(in 2006) is?",
"A": "China",
"B": "Canada",
"C": "South Africa",
"D": "USA",
"Answer": "South Africa"
},
{
"Question":"5. The largest country of the world by geographical area is?",
"A": "Russia",
"B": "Vatican City",
"C": "Australia",
"D": "USA",
"Answer": "Russia"
},
{
"Question":"6. The largest part of our hydrosphere is?",
"A": "Atlantic Ocean",
"B": "Indian Ocean",
"C": "Pacific Ocean",
"D": "Antarctica Ocean",
"Answer": "Pacific Ocean"
},
{
"Question":"7. Marathon is to race as hibernation is to?",
"A": "winter",
"B": "bear",
"C": "dream",
"D": "sleep",
"Answer": "sleep"
},
{
"Question":"8. Who invented the BALLPOINT PEN?",
"A": "Biro Brothers",
"B": "Waterman Brothers",
"C": "Bicc Brothers",
"D": "Write Brothers",
"Answer": "Biro Brothers"
},
{
"Question":"9. What Galileo invented?",
"A": "Barometer",
"B": "Pendulum clock",
"C": "Microscope",
"D": "Thermometer",
"Answer": "Thermometer"
},
{
"Question":"10. In which decade was the Internet first implemented?",
"A": "1940s",
"B": "1950s",
"C": "1960s",
"D": "1980s",
"Answer": "1960s"
}
]
